{
    "subject": "resource/Gombe_State",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Nigeria",
    "human_readable": "Gombe State is located in Nigeria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8886508345603943,
            "question": "Where is Gombe State located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6972789764404297,
            "question": "What country is Gombe State in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48538652062416077,
            "question": "What is the capital city of Gombe State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4388725757598877,
            "question": "Is Gombe State part of Africa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4100063741207123,
            "question": "What are some other states in Nigeria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3866557478904724,
            "question": "Can you name a state in Nigeria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3113633096218109,
            "question": "What are some of the main industries in Gombe State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3080196678638458,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Gombe State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2055162936449051,
            "question": "Are there any major rivers flowing through Gombe State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08596863597631454,
            "question": "Does Nigeria have any coastal regions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gombe State is located in Nigeria.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2106_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any major rivers flowing through Gombe State?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2106_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Gombe State?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2106_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the main industries in Gombe State?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2106_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2106_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the value as \"yes\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided clearly states that Gombe State, Nigeria has various local government areas and is governed by the All Progressives Congress (APC). Therefore, it supports the statement that Gombe State is located in Nigeria."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}